http://www.sharegrief.com/terms-and-conditions

grief counselling and coping with loss... because you are not alone.
Specialists' Login
Login:
Password:
Terms and Conditions of ShareGrief.com
ShareGrief.com is proud to welcome you to our website. Please take a few moments to read these Terms and Conditions prior to using this website. After reading this agreement, if you click on the "I agree", you are agreeing to the Terms and Conditions listed below. If you do not wish to be bound by this agreement, please do not use this website. Sharegrief.com may from time to time and without prior notice modify these terms and conditions, and thus you must verify the terms and conditions relating to use prior to each use of the web-site.General DisclaimerThe information provided by this site is for general information purposes only and is not intended to be a substitute for face-to-face professional advice. The content offered on the site is not a diagnosis or treatment of a mental or medical condition. You should not rely on the information contained on ShareGrief.com for medical, legal, or financial decisions. Do not disregard or delay seeking professional advice as a result of something you have read on this site. Seek the advice of a mental health professional in your area before making any decisions about treatment or medication.If you are feeling like you may be a danger to yourself or others, please contact a health-care professional or visit an emergency room or crisis center immediately.ShareGrief.com shall not assume any liability or responsibility for damage to property, injury or death to persons arising from any information provided on this site.ShareGrief.com is not responsible for delays or failure in performance resulting in acts beyond the control of ShareGrief.com . Such acts include acts of God, strikes, power failures, epidemics, fire, communicationline failures, or other disasters. ShareGrief.com is not liable or responsible for the conduct of other users or third parties.Links to Other WebsitesThis website may contain links to other websites. ShareGrief.com is not responsible for the content or performance of those sites. In addition, ShareGrief.com does not endorse any products that may appear on said sites.Public Forums (chatrooms and Message Boards)If you choose to participate in the public forums, you are solely responsible for your communications and the consequences of posting these communications. ShareGrief.com does not assume any responsibility for the consequences of such communications. In cases where you believe someone else is in danger, contact your local law enforcement agency immediately. ShareGrief.com reserves the right to remove, monitor, edit or delete any material deemed inappropriate. If you choose to participate in the public forums, the user agrees not to undertake any of the following actions:- Post material that is obscene, threatening, defamatory, misleading, hateful, or offensive- Post material that advocates illegal activity- Post material that infringes the intellectual property rights of others- Post advertising or business solicitation- Post chain letters, pyramid schemes, solicitations or petitions- Post any file or material which may contain viruses- Impersonate another person- Interfere with another person's participation in a forum- Violate privacy rights of othersShareGrief.com reserves the right to remove inappropriate communications and/or terminate a user's access to all public forums upon breach of Terms and Conditions. Also, it has the right to investigate any violation of this agreement.IndemnificationUser agrees to hold ShareGrief.com harmless from any dispute or legal proceeding relating to the use of the website or from information or material submitted or posted by the user or by anyone who has, by whatever means, acquired the user's password or arising from any breach of the terms and conditions of the agreement.JurisdictionThis agreement and the Terms and Conditions set forth are governed by the Canadian laws of the City of Montreal and Province of Quebec, Canada. Any mediation, legal actions, or arbitration shall be conducted in Montreal, Quebec, Canada. No other claims will be considered.ShareGrief.com may terminate the user's account and services when the above terms and conditions have been violated. For questions please contact contact@sharegrief.com.Privacy StatementShareGrief.com is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of its visitors. We understand that coping with the loss of a loved one can be a very personal and private matter. Therefore, protecting your privacy is extremely important to us. We urge you to read this policy to better understand how we safeguard your information.Our web site has been designed so that you can visit without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information at all. ShareGrief.com undertakes to adopt reasonable measures to protect the user's privacy but the user accepts that Sharegrief.com is not liable for any disclosure which occurs notwithstanding these reasonable efforts of Sharegrief.com. Sharegrief.com shall in no event be liable for information disclosed which is otherwise in the public domain or that can be obtained from other or public sources.Security and Protection of InformationIn order to use online therapy services, you must register and receive a user password. You are responsible to ensure that no person has access to your password. Once the user has indicated a desire to pursue online counselling, he/she must fill out the registration form indicating consent to participate in ShareGrief.com.We will only collect personal information from you if you voluntarily submit such information to us. We will never release your name, address or telephone number to any third party without your permission.Registration InformationWhen becoming a registered member of this site, users are asked to provide the following required information: Username/Password/e-mail addressAll personal information is otherwise private and will not be made available to any external party, company, or other users of the web site without consent of the user.The following exceptions apply:- We will release information about you or your account to comply with any legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order or in proceedings involving breach of the terms and conditions of this agreement.- If someone's life is in danger, the professional may choose to report it.- If you give out personal information on line (message board/chat room) that information can be collected and used by third parties. You disclose such information at your own risk.ShareGrief.com features bulletin boards which allows those with similar concerns to share information and support one another. We also offer online seminars moderated by our professional grief counsellor. Any information shared in these forums is public information. Please think carefully before disclosing personal information.Although ShareGrief.com is strongly committed to protecting your personal information, you should be aware that there are always sophisticated hackers who may find a way to bypass our security system and Sharegrief.com shall not be liable for any breach of privacy which occurs in spite of the reasonable precautions of Sharegrief.com.You may update or correct your personal information at any time by contacting us at: sandy@sharegrief.comBy registering on the ShareGrief.com web site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. Any changes to our policy will be posted on the site. Please refer back to this policy regularly.
Grief Support
Get grief support
Grief specialists
Request a guest speaker
Blog and Articles
Resources
Who We Are
About ShareGrief
Websites content ©ShareGrief 2011.
All Rights Reserved.
|
Web development ©Logograph software and services.
Licensed use only. www.logograph.com
